Good morning everyone!
This is Shiori Nagata from Nokotte Ikou Rumi.
Today's project is
Let's cook breakfast with Momochan!
Aiming for the ideal Japanese breakfast
We cooked!
We had a lot of happenings, but
but I think it turned out delicious.
Please take a look at it until the end.
Please take a look.
Okay, so...
I'm going to make miso soup.
Mr. White, let me wash your hands.
Yes!
Push!
Okay, I'm going to make miso soup now.
Yes! Good luck! Chikurin-chan!
Thank you so much! You're so supportive!
I made miso soup for the last time, and it was really for home economics class too!
Oh, you made miso soup!
How is it? This much?
Oh, it's good, right? I think it's good. It's great.
I think I'm gonna boil some water or something while I'm at it.
Whoa!
We should live.
He's so quiet.
Okay, I'll boil the water.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
A little hot water, but it'll go down, down, down.
I don't cook much at home.
That's right.
We often go out to eat together, right?
Basically.
We cook eggs and stuff.
That's why I'm making it today.
Like you're good at it.
You were doing a video earlier.
Tamagoyaki, my tamagoyaki shop.
I think it's delicious.
I'm looking forward to it!
I love omagoyaki.
I have to put back the wakame.
I can't put back the seaweed.
Efficiency? Efficiency?
I used to put the seaweed back in too much.
I got into trouble.
When I make off-line sushi.
I make it in a pot of hot water.
I put in a lot of water.
Really?
You like wakame?
I love it.
If you're not careful, wakame really grows.
That's right.
Maybe this is enough.
Yeah, yeah.
Can I really put some more in?
Sure.
Let's get a lot more wakame.
Maybe like this.
Great, great, great.
Just a little bit more.
Really? - Yeah. Yeah, but...
It's good, but it's gonna be a lot of water.
Okay, well, the water's just coming to a boil, so...
Oh! Great.
Let's get started.
Yay, yay, yay.
Yay!
I was thinking...
If we keep adding tofu...
That's right.
I put the green onions in at the end, too.
You put the green onions in last, too, don't you?
That's right.
When should I put wakame seaweed in?
I should put miso in.
That's right.
It's written in the manual of this divination
How to make miso soup
Oh, it's written here, it's here, it's here, it's here!
Oh, it's right.
Put it in first.
Put it all in.
Then, I'm going to put in more flavor.
Go for it, go for it, go for it.
Go for it, I made it.
Oh!
Oh, I ate it.
It turned into miso soup.
That's true.
Miso soup has a strong flavor
Oh, I like it thick, and it's turned into a soup.
I like it strong.
We like it strong.
Taste is...
I think it's about this much.
It looks really delicious.
What do you think?
He's a genius!
I'll keep the miso soup warm for now.
I'm going to make an omelet.
I was looking forward to it the most!
This frying pan is so big!
Amazing, isn't it?
I'm going to use about 4 pans.
With Yoochalo's omelets, you can use as many as you want.
Crack them lengthwise?
I thought I messed up.
We don't put the shells in.
I promise.
It's been a while since I've seen Momo.
She's starting to give me presents.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Sorry, Momo-san... do you cook? It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Momo-san, do you cook?
I cook when I have to.
Lately...
We've been going out to eat beef, right?
I put sugar in it.
It's sweet.
Hang in there, hang in there, chicoryta.
I know I say "chicoryta" a lot.
If someone who's never seen me before...
If they hear me say it for the first time...
They'll be like, "Hurrah!
Because, you know...
I still don't know where I'm from.
I still don't know where I'm from
I don't know anyone who knows where it comes from.
Yes! That's right.
Chi-chan and Kachi-chan...
I'm the only one who knows.
Chikorinta.
She's got a certain something about her.
That's right.
But no one knows where it comes from.
So I often turn around when someone calls me Hee-chan.
Hee-chan?
Hee-chan sounds like "Chi Chi" or "Chi-chan.
Oh, I see.
How's it going? It's nice, isn't it?
Yeah, it's good.
I think I'm going to open it. How's it going? - It's good, isn't it? It looks good, doesn't it?
Okay, I'm going to fry up some eggs.
Like this?
Yeah!
What kind of omelet will it be?
Smile when it gets brown.
Yes, of course, I'll practice laughing.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh! I think it's warming up! Yeah, of course I'll practice laughing.
I think it's warming me up.
Hang in there, hang in there, I want to make it.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
Oh, yummy.
Looks delicious.
Looks good already!
Oh, I'm going to make it like this.
Oh, my God.
I put too much oil in.
Oh, yeah.
Well, well, well, well, well, well...
let's give it a try... let's give it a try... we got too much oil...
Let's give it a try
Let's pull in one more time.
That's right... you didn't pull it in.
That's right.
I don't know why...
Now, you see...
It's pretty crispy.
I wonder why.
Why? But, you know, it's only the first step, so I can handle it.
Why not?
I can't do it.
But, but, but, but..,
Let's compress it.
It looks fluffy and delicious,
I feel like I want to bite into it all at once.
Yay!
Thank you so much for all your support.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I think this one looks really good.
It'll look even better when it's cut.
I know, right?
Next!
I'm gonna make chocolate Sala wiener.
Can you make choco sala wiener?
Can you make it? I'm going to make it!
Chawesen's
I like Chawesen the best!
I love it!
I love it.
If you put a cross here...
I can't open it anymore.
I think it's Mr. Motako.
I think my legs are going to start flapping.
Oh!
Put some salt and pepper on it.
I'll put some salt and pepper on it.
Oh, that's good.
Okay, bye.
I'd like to cut it, but where do you want to cut it? Do you want me to stand up a little? Yeah, I'll be right there.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, I'd like to cut it.
Where do you want to cut it?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe I'll just take a picture of it and then it'll look like a big mess.
That's right.
I'll cut it here first.
There it is! Nice section! Nice section!
Oh, yes!
Let's put the beautiful blue ones on the table and have a taste of this one!
Yes!
First thing in the morning, it's a good breakfast!
How about the salmon?
Can I taste it?
Oh! Yummy!
Put this on too!
Here we go! Ready!
Ooh! Breakfast! I love breakfast! Ready! Ooh!
Breakfast!
This is so stylish!
The serving is complete!
Yay! Yay!
And now...
I'd like to take it to the table
I'd like to take it to the table.
Yeah!
Ready! I'll have some miso soup! I'll have some miso soup! I'll have some miso soup! I'm having miso soup!
Bon appétit!
I'll start with the wakame.
Thank you for your cooperation!
Delicious!
I love miso soup!
I like it!
The green onions are crunchy, too.
Good!
Nice and thick.
So this is when the Chinese lessons come in.
You're going to put it in your idol activity.
Yes, I do.
Okay, maybe some salmon.
Tama no Yaki... you've been here recently.
Can I go? Can I go? Can I go? - Yeah!
That's for sure.
Can I go?
Tamago charcoal.
I'll have the tamagoyaki, then.
Bon appétit.
I'm going to have some of mommy's snacks.
Let's have some rice.
It's too good.
Oh, by the way...
Today's loungewear.
Look at that!
It's a loungewear today!
Hey!
We went shopping together, right?
That's why...
We bought it together.
We paid the bill together.
Like mine.
The pink one is definitely mine.
That's why I bought this one.
I didn't say which was which.
I got the pink one.
There must be something about the pink one.
Everything I own is pink.
It was pink.
That was a lot of fun.
It was fun.
We did a lot of stuff together.
Yeah, we did.
You have a lot to talk about.
Yes, we do.
But the things we talk about...
We've already talked about it.
That's right.
That's why I don't remember what we talked about.
Yesterday, when we were having a conversation, we talked about... something... but if you say "but" too much, it's not good.
I think we're trying to find words to replace "but". What happened to you?
What happened to you? No, no, no, no!
My heart's in knots!
I don't remember anything else!
Yesterday's conversation
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
Just now.
Earlier, delicious!
Salt and pepper.
The syrup is delicious and the salt and pepper are good.
I have a memory.
I've been a lot of places.
Where did you two go?
The two of us.
We went to Atami.
You never talk about it.
One day, out of the blue.
One day after class.
We decided to go to Atami.
It was really sudden, wasn't it?
That's right.
That's right. He said he only thought about going soon.
We just made up our minds right then and there.
Right?
That's it, right?
We went to the beach early in the morning to watch the sunrise.
Let's go to the beach early in the morning to watch the sunrise.
We went to a bar, bought some tidbits, and made a toast.
We went to a bar, bought tidbits, and made a toast.
That was pretty memorable. It feels like a school trip.
I want to go away again.
We went to Hiroshima, too.
That's a good idea.
The chickie was impressed by all the billboards.
That's right!
And E was impressed by a supermarket in Hiroshima called Every.
There's a supermarket in Hiroshima called Every.
Every's music inside the store is really good.
I used to sing that song a lot, and Momochan learned it.
We sing together.
You go on many dates, don't you?
Yes, we do.
Next time we do a concert in Hiroshima...
If we do a concert together...
All of us.
Live.
I'm so happy
Please eat you
Eat you, everyone.
Yes, sir
That's why
We could eat it together.
I was happy
I was so happy
It was delicious.
I ate it.
It was the best meal I've had today.
So...
I wish all of you who are watching this video a good day.
I wish you a good day!
Let's end with something.
Havana chair
Let's do it!
Havana Ice Day